[
  {
    "Question": "Which character type is strong against Blast type?",
    "Answer": "Speed"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What material is Captain America's shield made of?",
    "Answer": "Vibranium"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the function that uses a character’s Biometrics to increase a character’s rank?",
    "Answer": "Rank Up"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the special item that can be equipped to Heroes to gain stats and special abilities?",
    "Answer": "Custom Gear"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Canadian character with superhuman abilities is called the \"Merc with a Mouth\"?",
    "Answer": "Deadpool"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the advanced material needed to upgrade Gear that is at least +10?",
    "Answer": "Dimension Debris"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the skill that reduces all defence and removes all buffs from the enemy?",
    "Answer": "Incapacitation"
  },
  {
    "Question": "From the available character skill effects, what is the ability that blocks damage and debuffs but causes the character to receive effects like Guard Break?",
    "Answer": "Immune To All Damage"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the term for the amount of damage received, regardless of a character’s defense and Type Resistance?",
    "Answer": "True Damage"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the material used to Rank Up X-Men?",
    "Answer": "X-Gene"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What materials are not required to upgrade a character to Tier-3?",
    "Answer": "Norn Stone of Chaos"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the ability that groups enemies together and prevents them from moving for a duration of time, rendering them unable to use basic attacks or use skills?",
    "Answer": "Bind"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which mode grows your heroes while exploring their journey and backstory?",
    "Answer": "Epic Quest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What materials are NOT required to upgrade a character to Tier-3?",
    "Answer": "Type Enhancer"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the skill effect that decreases Physical Damage received?",
    "Answer": "Elasticity"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the character who is called the Sorcerer Supreme?",
    "Answer": "Doctor Strange"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is NOT one of Spider-man's abilities?",
    "Answer": "Communicating with Spiders"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the function that can further enhance the stats of the equipped Uru?",
    "Answer": "Uru Amplification"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following nicknames are not Hawkeye?",
    "Answer": "Magic Eye"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the substance that caused Dr. Bruce Banner to turn into Hulk?",
    "Answer": "Gamma Radiation"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the basic material needed for Gear Upgrades?",
    "Answer": "Gear Up Kit"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the stat that gives a passive-like effect to all heroes just by being on the team?",
    "Answer": "Team Passive"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where was Loki born?",
    "Answer": "Jotunheim"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the function that uses 2 Uru as material to create a different type of Uru?",
    "Answer": "Combine Uru"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the skill that reduces all enemy attack?",
    "Answer": "Fracture"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can you obtain Chaos Tokens and various rewards by battling a powerful boss in varying difficulties of Easy, Medium, and Hard?",
    "Answer": "Villain Siege"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the material used to Advance X-Men to Tier-2?",
    "Answer": "Phoenix Feather"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the story-based quests that explore a certain character's journey?",
    "Answer": "Epic Quest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the gear often obtained from Special Missions that gives a special stat to each character when equipped?",
    "Answer": "Custom Gear"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What content opens during specific hours of the day and allows Agents to battle with the same Character conditions?",
    "Answer": "World Event"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of following is not an Infinity Stone?",
    "Answer": "Eternal Stone"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the function that imbues a special effect when ISO-8s are equipped onto characters in a specific formation?",
    "Answer": "Iso-8 Set Bonus"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What Character has never actually served as Captain America?",
    "Answer": "T'Challa"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What institution trained Black Widow?",
    "Answer": "Red Room"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which mode is open every day and allows Agents to battle with the same character conditions?",
    "Answer": "World Event"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What materials are needed when increasing Mastery of a Character?",
    "Answer": "Norn Stone"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the item that can be equipped (up to a max of 5) on character gear, and can be strengthened using Ampliﬁcation?",
    "Answer": "Enchanted Uru"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the tunnel that connects Yggdrasil's nine realms?",
    "Answer": "Bifrost"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following characters is not a Guardian of the Black Order?",
    "Answer": "Hypergiant"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Iron Man's Real name?",
    "Answer": "Tony Stark"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the material used to Recruit or Rank Up characters?",
    "Answer": "Biometrics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the mode for which you can earn additional rewards using hidden tickets?",
    "Answer": "Dimension Mission"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the skill effect that removes targeting and prevents a character from taking damage?",
    "Answer": "Ignore Targeting"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can you battle other users using a set team of 3 and get Honor Tokens as rewards?",
    "Answer": "Timeline Battle"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the Effect gained when a team is assembled with specific characters?",
    "Answer": "Team Bonus"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following characters is not a Guardian of the Galaxy?",
    "Answer": "Quicksilver"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the stat that raises Critical Rate by a guaranteed fixed amount, regardless of the opponent’s level?",
    "Answer": "Guaranteed Critical Rate Increase"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the ability that grants immunity to all damage (basic attacks, Guard Break, Damage, Debuffs)?",
    "Answer": "Invincible"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can you obtain items like Dimension Debris, Comic Cards, and Uniform Kits?",
    "Answer": "Dimension Rift"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the real-time co-op content that pits players against a powerful boss?",
    "Answer": "Giant Boss Raid"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the ability that puts enemies in fear for a duration of time, rendering them unable to attack or use skills?",
    "Answer": "Fear"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the shop where you can acquire rewards using Rift Tokens in Dimension Mission?",
    "Answer": "Support Shop"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Wolverine's quick regenerative ability?",
    "Answer": "Healing Factor"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the material that can raise X-Men mastery?",
    "Answer": "M'kraan Shard"
  },
  {
    "Question": "From the available character skill effects, what is the ability that blocks damage but causes the character to receive effects like Guard Break and debuffs?",
    "Answer": "Shield"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the ability that charms opponents for a set duration, rendering them unable to move, attack, even preventing automatically activated attacks from activating?",
    "Answer": "Charm"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a weapon NOT associated with Thor?",
    "Answer": "Axe of Angarruumus"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the material that can further enhance character stats when equipped to Grade 20 Gear?",
    "Answer": "Enchanted Uru"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the item that increases all characters’ stats and is usually obtainable from Dimension Rift?",
    "Answer": "Comic Cards"
  },
  {
    "Question": "From the available character skill effects, what is the ability that causes the character to receive damage but stops effects like Guard Break?",
    "Answer": "Super Armor"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the character who is a member of the Air Force and one of Tony Stark's good Friends?",
    "Answer": "James Rupert Rhodes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the content that has Anti-Matter Collection, the Item Shop, and the ability to use Deploy?",
    "Answer": "S.H.I.E.L.D. Lab"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the chapter-based quests that can be cleared in order for rewards?",
    "Answer": "Heroic Quest"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the ability that cancels an opponent’s skill by forcing them to make a basic attack?",
    "Answer": "Guard Break"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Odin's horse?",
    "Answer": "Sleipnir"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of an item that can be equipped up to 8 times to increase various stats and receive special set effects?",
    "Answer": "ISO-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the Challenge that gives rewards by solving special challenges daily?",
    "Answer": "Challenges"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the character wielding superhuman strength who also happens to be the king of Wakanda?",
    "Answer": "Black Panther"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can you obtain EXP Chips and Biometrics and also claim additional rewards by clearing a Hidden Route in certain stages?",
    "Answer": "Special Mission"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of items made with Marvel comic covers that can be equipped with up to 5 items per account to increase the stats of all heroes?",
    "Answer": "Comic Cards"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where was Loki Born?",
    "Answer": "Jotunheim"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Character is NOT a member of the Black Order?",
    "Answer": "Hypergiant"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What Character Type is typically strong against Speed Type Characters?",
    "Answer": "Combat"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of these isn't a name for Hawkeye?",
    "Answer": "Magic Eye"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the function that allows Tier-1 characters to become Tier-2?",
    "Answer": "Advancement"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the metal in Wolverine's skeleton?",
    "Answer": "Adamantium"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of the stat that raises Dodge Rate by a guaranteed fixed amount, regardless of the difference in opponent level?",
    "Answer": "Guaranteed Dodge Rate Increase"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which is not one of Ant-man's abilities?",
    "Answer": "Thermokinesis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which character type is strong against Combat type?",
    "Answer": "Blast"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the ability that locks opponents in time for a set duration, preventing them from moving, attacking, or dodging?",
    "Answer": "Time Freezing"
  }
]